{
    "subject": "resource/Karen_K._Caldwell",
    "predicate": "property/appointer",
    "object": "resource/List_of_federal_judges_appointed_by_George_W._Bush",
    "human_readable": "Karen K. Caldwell was appointed by George W. Bush.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9577910304069519,
            "question": "Who appointed Karen K. Caldwell?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9479172825813293,
            "question": "Were there any notable events during George W. Bush's presidency that relate to Karen K. Caldwell's appointment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9345009922981262,
            "question": "What position was Karen K. Caldwell appointed to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7752700448036194,
            "question": "What were the qualifications or background of Karen K. Caldwell that led to her appointment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.636881411075592,
            "question": "How did Karen K. Caldwell's appointment impact her field or area of expertise?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6312113404273987,
            "question": "Are there any controversies or debates surrounding Karen K. Caldwell's appointment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5198551416397095,
            "question": "What is known about Karen K. Caldwell's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49592506885528564,
            "question": "Who was George W. Bush?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46284422278404236,
            "question": "What are some examples of other appointments made by George W. Bush?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31587979197502136,
            "question": "During what period was George W. Bush in office?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Karen K. Caldwell was appointed by George W. Bush.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7373_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of other appointments made by George W. Bush?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7373_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was George W. Bush?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7373_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Karen K. Caldwell's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7373_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7373_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7373_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7373_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7373_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7373_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7373_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7373_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7373_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7373_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7373_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents mention that \"On the recommendation of Senators Mitch McConnell and Jim Bunning, Caldwell was nominated to the United States District Court for the Eastern District of Kentucky by President George W. Bush on September 4, 2001...\" and also that \"Caldwell entered into private practice in the State of Kentucky from 1993 to 2001 and also served as an Adjunct Professor at Transylvania University in 2000... The nomination sailed through Senate confirmation hearings, and she was sworn in on November 30, 2001.\"\n\nThis suggests that President George W. Bush did appoint Karen K. Caldwell."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that Karen K. Caldwell was nominated and confirmed as a United States District Judge for the Eastern District of Kentucky by President George W. Bush on September 4, 2001, with her confirmation date set on October 23, 2001."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}